哦  我真激动
Oh, I am so excited
你将在四频道的节日晚会上担任领衔主演
that you're headlining channel four's holiday spectacular.
部分原因是这事儿有利于小镇
Partly because it's great for the town,
但最主要的原因是我已经告诉组委会你会答应
but mostly because I'd already told the committee you'd say yes.
我的意思是怎么好意思说不呢
I mean, how can I say no?
这里是一切开始的地方  就在八年前
This is where it all began eight years ago.
我的小宝贝儿第一次站在舞台上
My little baby's first time out on stage
唱出她的心声
singing her little heart out.
我还记得你唱"寒冷的雪人"时使大家惊讶的情景
I still remember how you wowed the crowd with "Frosty the Snowman".
还有唱"白色圣诞节"那首歌时
And "White Christmas".
还有"小小鼓手"
And "Little Drummer Boy".
你唱完"哦  耶路撒冷的小镇"的时候
By the time you'd finished "O Little Town of Bethlehem,"
我感觉就像独自走到了那里
I felt like I'd walked there myself.
我不想唱完
I never wanted it to end.
确实几乎没唱完
And it almost didn't.
丽芙・鲁尼
Liv Rooney?
你好  我是珍妮・基恩
Hi. I'm Jenny Keene.
你好  你就是那个要和我在平安夜
Hi. You are the adorable little girl that I get
同台演出的可爱小女孩吧
to share the stage with this Christmas Eve.
我看过你的试唱录像  亲  你确实不错
I watched your audition tape, and you have some serious pipes, young lady.
有天赋的感觉真爽  是不
It feels so good to be talented, doesn't it?
我长大了就要像你一样
I want to be just like you when I grow up.
那你确实走对了路
Well, you are certainly on the right track.
八年前  我和你一样
Eight years ago, I was you.
我还是那个眼睛里闪着光的小女孩
I was a starry-eyed little girl,
第一次在电视上露面  很激动呢
excited to make her first TV appearance.
节目结束后我的生活永远地发生了改变
And I mean, after this show, my life changed forever.
这是真的  没有它  丽芙永远不会拍摄本地的广告
t's true. Without it, Liv never would have been cast
在其中扮演歌唱消音器的曼迪
in a local commercial as Mandy, the singing muffler.
清清嗓子
[Clears throat]
曼迪说您的消音器顶级好
Mandy says your muffler is a-okay.
我们至今还享受打折优惠呢
We still get a discount.
但我当时确实没有引导我的人  所以我想成为你的引导者
But I didn't really have anyone to guide me, so I wanted to be that for you.
你也知道  这一行会有点难  最好能有个导师
You know, this industry can get kind of tough, and it's good to have a mentor.
真是难以置信丽芙・鲁尼将成为我的名人导师
I can't believe Liv Rooney's going to be my celebrity mentor.
哦  别叫  名人导师
Oh, stop. Celebrity mentor?
你不必那样叫我
You don't have to say that...
我的意思是  要是你非要那样叫我
I mean, you definitely can.
我也不反对
I'm not gonna stop you.